# **Roland Emojevbe**

UX/UI Product Designer | London, UK | Open to Relocating

+44 7851 383558

roland.emojevbe@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/roland-emojevbe

www.behance.net/rolandemojevbe

### **Profile**

UX/UI designer with a background in management consulting and a passion for creating intuitive and beautiful designs. Experienced in problem-solving and using data to help businesses develop their strategies. Skilled in interpersonal relationship building and communicating with a variety of stakeholders.

### **UX Skills**

- Competitive Analysis
- User Research, Personas and Mind-Mapping
- User Interviews and User Testing
- Information Architecture
- Wireframing and Iterative Prototyping
- UI Design, style guide creation/management

### **Technical Skills**

- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- Sketch
- Figma
- HTML
- Word, Excel, PowerPoint and other Microsoft Office suite
- Confluence
- Jira

### **Education**

### **Frontend Development for Designers**

(fully coded my own portfolio website)
CareerFoundry
Jan 2020 - Mar 2021

### **UX Design Certification**

CareerFoundry
Apr 2020 - Dec 2020

#### **BSc Economics and Finance**

(including a year in industry)
University of Surrey
Oct 2013 – Jul 2017

## **UX Projects**

### **Search Party: Location Scavenger Hunt App**

Mobile first responsive web application: May 2020 - Dec 2020

- Utilised the design thinking process to create usercentred designs that solved users' problems.
- Built a multi-feature solution based on competitive analysis using Adobe XD, Photoshop, Optimal Workshop, Usability Hub.
- Conducted usability testing and iterated on low-, midand high-fidelity prototypes.
- Created a style guide, design language system and prepared deliverables for development handoff.

### HoliPrep: Vocabulary Learning App

Mobile application: Apr 2020 - May 2020

- Conducted five user interviews and utilised user research to develop a pronto persona, user flows and task analyses.
- Used results of usability testing to develop higher-fidelity prototypes using Sketch.
- Presented the process and journey of building the product to stakeholders.

### **Experience**

### **Customer Experience Consultant**

Veriteer, London: Aug 2020 - Present

- Part of the UX and Mobile App teams of a global retailer.
- Regularly conducting user research and competitor benchmarking before the wireframing of a new story.
- Providing analysis to ensure all design decisions remain data driven.
- Creating visuals for some UX improvement proposals.

#### **Management Consultant**

Helios, Farnborough: Oct 2017 - Jul 2020

- Led a variety of international projects and teams, focused on - business strategy and performance.
- Worked closely with clients' executive board, carrying out in-depth research, stakeholder interviews and leading onsite client workshops.
- Ensured quality data analysis and report writing, whilst ensuring timely delivery of the teams' outputs within budget.

### **Group Tax/Treasury Junior Analyst**

SABMiller, Woking, Aug 2015 - Aug 2016

- Created work instructions and successfully taught team members how to complete a month-end process.
- Implemented an optimisation process that created twofold benefits for the organisation.